[Music]
Hey, did you know that Microsoft
AppSource has over 7,000 add-ons for
Business Central? If you're a Microsoft
partner and you publish add-on apps on
AppSource or custom solutions for your
customers, you know how important it is
to take the time to help each user get
started with your solution, configure
those new features that you've released,
and help them get past issues quickly.
Now, we love that our partner community
has the same customer passion as we do,
but we also know doing that at scale and
around the clock can be challenging and
can be really timeconuming as well. My
name is Mike and in these next 5 minutes
um I'm going to show you how partners
can lower their support costs when
Copilot knows about their apps. I'm
going to show you how that works. Uh
Copilot and Business Central can now
answer questions based on the apps that
are installed on that environment. Um,
that's essentially your add-ons that you
have built. It helps users learn new
skills quickly. Uh, it helps them get
unblocked self-sufficiently as well
without having to contact you. And
that's the most important point. So,
first let's check out how people
experience this inside Business Central.
So, let's imagine my team has just
installed a project management add-on
for Business Central from a publisher
named Fabricam. And I'm curious about
this app. So, let's ask Copilot for some
help. We'll bring up the copilot pane.
Now, because I'm going to do quite a bit
of chatting, I'm going to just stretch
the pane and give me maximum size and
type what is this fabricam app.
Now, here copilot is off looking for an
answer for me and it comes back with a
very short um a very short message
saying that this is the fabric project
management app. It's an advanced
extension for business central uh uses
copilot, automates repetitive project
setup tasks and so on and so forth.
Fantastic. That's really good news cuz
that's just what I was looking for. But
let me now ask for some advanced
functionality like can I choose pools by
department. So again, Copilot will go
and try and find an answer for me. Now
keep in mind this is not standard
business central functionality. This is
coming from this particular app.
Copilot says yes you can choose resource
pools by department. Excellent. It tells
me a little bit more about that such as
I can do it by region or expertise as
well. And maybe I've also encountered an
error where setting things up. So my
style of question would be how do I
solve invalid resource pool ID errors in
fabricam?
And again copilot will look up that
information and present a response. So
here you can see how um copilot has also
helped me not just understand the root
cause of that error but in this case
also provide tips about how I may get
past it myself. What's the solution to
this error? Now, you may have noticed
that all throughout we have citations,
we have references for each of these
answers. And that's because every
response that Copilot gave me here is
grounded in the documentation that
accompanies the Fabricam app that I have
installed. Essentially, it's using that
documentation as the source for all of
these answers. And that documentation is
your documentation. Let's zoom into that
a bit. So, first of all, how does
Copilot even know about my app? Well, to
answer my questions, Copilot first has
found the list of installed apps that
are contextually relevant to that
environment. Next, for each of those
apps, it's found the help link, the
docu, the link to documentation for that
specific app. Um, and then it's
transformed my question into a set of
search terms and it's used Microsoft
Bing search to actually search that
website specifically and only that
website for answers. Um, that's all
powered by Microsoft Bing behind the
scenes. And finally, those search
results come back and Copilot uses AI to
turn that into a response along with
those citations and references that I
showed you earlier. Now, Fabricam
project management is of course a sample
app that I built myself to illustrate
how this works. So, how about your app?
How will it work for you? Well, Copilot
might already be able to answer
questions about your apps if you've
already linked them to your online
documentation. um that might be ready to
go with no additional effort from your
part. Uh so install your app, give it a
try and find out if you're ready to go.
If you do see that copilot is struggling
with some of the answers, I want to
share some tips with you on how you can
get your online documentation ready for
Copilot. So first of all, you need to
make sure that your app.json file has a
help property pointing to your online
documentation. And remember, you're
accountable for what's at the end of
that link. Uh next this works using
Microsoft Bing. So your site needs to be
accessible uh with Microsoft Bing. It
needs to be indexed by Bing. Um which
means the site has to be public. Uh
there can't be any authentication you
know password walls that you need to get
through. Copilot can't get through any
uh login screens. Even if you need to
log in with the same users um enter ID
for authentication. So this can't be um
your internet site, it can't be your
local SharePoint site. it has to be
publicly available on the internet. Uh,
and use Bing's web master tools. That's
a great set of tools to help you make
sure that the right sites are indexed
and accelerate some of that process. Be
aware that it can take uh sometimes a
few days from when you publish a new
site or make edits until they're
discoverable by Bing as well as Copilot.
Next is site structure. Don't go too
deep with the structure of your articles
on your on your website. uh ultimately
copilot will search what's at the URL
you defined in that help property and up
to two levels down as well. So you may
need to restructure your content to
support how copilot operates. Um if
you're using redirection for example URL
shorteners be aware that copilot gets
confused by that. So if you're
redirecting to a whole different domain
or different site uh it won't work. And
finally format and this is also really
interesting uh for our partner
community. So, Copilot works primarily
with text and that means it's going to
ignore any illustrations, any icons that
you have on your help site. Um, but it
does work with Excel and PDF files. So,
if you have hosted files like that on
your website, Copilot will actually be
able to find the information inside them
and use that to provide answers to your
customers as well. One last tip. After
you install the app and you've tried it
out, try to be a bit methodical about
testing different aspects of how users
may ask questions for your app. For
example, uh try and hit different levels
of sub uh uh subp partaths in your
documentation. Uh try to ask different
types and styles of questions about you
know what is the app and what can it do
for me or tell me more about this
functionality and how do I set it up? or
for troubleshooting. Here's the error
symptom. What's the root cause and
what's the mitigation to get past that?
How do I fix it? Try all of that of
those out. Do it a bit more methodically
to get a good sense of how Copilot works
with your content. Now, if you're
looking for more details and examples of
good and not so good URLs you can use
for that help link, um, check out the
links I put below this video. uh you'll
learn one how to prepare your app uh
content for copilot and also how Bing
search works for this and other features
in Business Central. So we really think
our customers will find this useful if
they're new to Business Central, maybe
new to your app or learning how to
configure those new features or just
trying to learn those expert tips and
tricks to help them through their day.
Uh in fact, we're looking forward to
evolving this concept even further to
provide much better support for our
customers in the future. Uh, and your
online documentation for your apps here
is truly key. It's super important that
you get those in shape for copilot.
So, this is the end of this video. We
hope you enjoyed it. Hope you learned
something new. So, do like and subscribe
if you want to see more of these. Um,
and thank you so much for watching.